## **ROBBIE PARR**

Robbie Parr, just finished his third and final year at the University of York studying for a BEng in Computer Science. With over 7 years Python programming experience, React Native cross platform app development and 3D/VR Game development. He is very keen and motivated to learn new programming languages and frameworks, if he doesn't currently have a skill you want, he'll just go away and learn it. Regularly designing small projects to code in newly learnt environments or languages. Being very organised and reliable with good communication, team working and problem-solving skills, making him an invaluable member of any team. In the past he has undertaken leadership roles and have encouraged team bonding, as President of Baking Society, which improved team cohesion and performance at stress points in the project/group. He is looking for his first graduate job starting September 2023.

#### **Key Technical Skills**

- Strong Programming in Python, Java and Haskell
- Other Programming in C & C++, C#, HTML, CSS, SCSS and JavaScript, R
- App development using React and React Native (With TailwindCSS Styling, Expo Deployment)
- Continuous Integration and Project Management in Git (GitHub)
- Code Architecture in UML
- Databases using Firebase, Sanity and SQLite (Using SQL and XML)
- App Modelling in Balsamiq Wireframes
- Games design using Unity, 3D modelling using Blender
- File storage and forms using Google Drive (Docs, Slides, Sheets, Sites)

#### **Key Transferable skills**

- Leadership
- Responsible
- Punctual
- Organised
- Problem Solving
- Efficient
- Hard Working
- Trustworthy
- Adaptable
- Adept Mathematically

- Adept Scientifically (Especially in Physics)
- Technologically Adept
- Diligence
- Dependable
- Discretion
- Perseverance
- Resilience
- Resourceful
- Reliable

#### **Experience**

York Community Consulting	October 2022 - Current	
Joined a technology focussed consultancy project in October	What I learnt	
2022 as a Senior Consultant and upon completion of the project	Learnt about how to build a client facing	
was promoted to a Software Developer in the wider YCC	ReactJS/Next.Js web application. Utilising	
Technology team to continue developing the new YCC website.	Agile methodologies and kanban boards	
The website utilises React.JS/Next.Js, SCSS, JSX with a JavaScript	for team organisation and progress	
backend and firebase data and API endpoints.	tracking.	

University of York, Baking Society	Three University Terms (1 Year) 18th March 2021 - 24th March 2022	
I was the President of the Baking Society, where I was	What I learnt	
tasked with organising society events and organising the	What it's like to be in a leadership role, the	
society as a whole. Hosting events and being the face of	importance of good relationships with society	
the society. For my year long term.	members and members of small businesses.	

# **ROBBIE PARR**

The Edinburgh Woollen Mill (Horsham Town Centre Branch)		23rd February 2020 - 20th September 2020
Worked as a Sales Assistant for the store. Helping with the selling of goods to customers. Ensuring a excellent customer experience.	What I learnt	
	· ·	ney handling and till experience), If help people out and how to mer experience.

Aston University, Headstart Course		15 <sup>th</sup> July 2019 – 18 <sup>th</sup> July 2019
An Headstart Course, working in a very small team	What I learnt	
we were taught how to use a JavaScript framework	How to work as part of a team to plan and finish a	
to create a game based around Recycling.	small game with limited time and resources.	

Shelton Develo	pment Services (Cranleigh)	31 July –	4 August 2017
One-week work	What I learnt		References
experience writing	I learnt what it was like to work in a professional		
software using Python,	environment. How to work effectively and		Head of Software Team /
Pygame, HTML and CSS to re-create a licence system for the company's	efficiently in a team. But the experience of what an average week could look and feel like after I have finished my degree was invaluable		Software Architect, Mr Fred Trüter: fred@s-d- s.co.uk
software products.	, 25,000		

### **Education**

Universit	y of York	Degree	
BEng in Computer	Third year complete, results pending		2 <sup>nd</sup> Year Average 2:1
Science			Classification

Collyers (College of Richard Collyer)		A Levels
Subject	Final Grade	Education Dates
Computer Science	A*	September 2018 - August 2020
Physics	А	September 2018 - August 2020
Mathematics (Single)	A*	September 2018 - August 2020
EPQ: Artefact	В	July 2019 - August 2020